I've stored the "Our Amazing Community" heading,
لقد قمت بتخزين العنوان "Our Amazing Community"،
this DOM element, into the heading variable.
عنصر DOM هذا، في المتغير "the heading".
Now let's use the "classList" property to fiddle around with this DOM element.
لنستخدم الآن الخاصية "classList" للتعامل مع عنصر DOM هذا.
We can see that this DOM element has a class attribute with the class "text-center",
يمكننا رؤية أن عنصر DOM هذا يتضمن سمة "class" مع الفئة "text-center"،
but we can have the "classList" property tell us that.
غير أنه يمكننا أن نجعل الخاصية "classList" تُخبرنا بذلك.
Checking to see if the heading contains this class,
يمكنكم التحقق لمعرفة ما إذا كان العنوان يحتوي على هذه الفئة،
this tells us it does.
ويخبرنا ذلك بأنه يحتوي عليها.
Let's add our own class.
دعونا نضيف فئتنا الخاصة.
Using the "classList" property's "add" property,
باستخدام الخاصية "classList" والخاصية "add"،
we can say add the "ice cream" class,
يمكننا أن نقول إضافة الفئة "ice cream"،
and we can see that it added it up here.
ويمكننا رؤية أنها تمت إضافتها بالأعلى هنا.
Now we don't have any styling for the "ice cream" class,
ليس لدينا الآن أنماط للفئة "ice cream"،
but it's still been added. Let's remove that.
لكنها لازالت مضافة. دعونا نحذف ذلك.
And calling "remove", and passing the class we want to remove,
ونقوم باستدعاء "remove" وتمرير الفئة التي نودُّ حذفها،
we can see it removed that "ice cream" class.
ويمكننا رؤية أنها قد حذفت الفئة "ice cream".
And last, but definitely not least,
والأمر الأخير، ولكن بالتأكيد ليس آخراً،
is the "toggle method."
هو "toggle method.&lrm;"
Toggling it once takes it off,
تبديلها مرة واحدة يؤدي إلى إزالتها،
and toggling it again puts it back on.
وتبديلها مرة أخرى يؤدي إلى عودتها.